《Feel You Now》 - Alessia Cara
♪ 我找到的这线微光 ♪
♪ This little light I've found ♪
♪ 吸进 呼出 ♪
♪ Take it in, breathe it out ♪
♪ 鼓虽小 声却响 ♪
♪ A little drum that's beating loud ♪
♪ 透过胸口 我听到了声响 ♪
♪ In my chest, I hear the sound ♪
♪ 我能感觉到 ♪
♪ I can feel ♪
♪ 感觉到你了 ♪
♪ Feel you now ♪
♪我现在能感觉到你  ♪
♪ I can feel you now ♪
♪ 我能感觉到 ♪
♪ I can feel ♪
♪ 我现在能感觉到你 ♪
♪ I can feel you now ♪
银 翼 杀 手
黑   莲   花
米德摄像机
翻译  Chenfan
时间轴  Chenfan
我在哪
Where am I?
你干嘛
Hey! What the hell?
你对我做了什么
What did you do to me?
救了你一命
Saved your life.
你用电枪电我
You shot me with a stun gun.
是你杀了班尼斯特 对吧
Killed Bannister, didn't you?
别担心 我不会出卖你的
Don't worry. I won't turn you in.
你当时失去了理智
You were out of control.
我不得不这么做
I did what I had to do.
我的设备
My device.
我说到做到
I always finish a job.
你怎么知道我在那
How did you know you'd find me there?
AS-08报告
AS-08 reporting.
返回现场 完毕
Returning to scene. Over.
收到
Roger that.
有人报警说在鹌鹑大厦附近有多声枪响
Report of multiple gunshots heard near the Quail building.
我调到警用频道
I was tuned into the police frequency.
得知班尼斯特参议员被人谋杀
Picked up chatter about Senator Bannister's murder.
我就猜是你
Just put two and two together.
那我真该感谢你
I guess I'm supposed to say thank you.
来 把它喝了
Here. Drink this.
不怪你
Don't blame you.
大断电后 酒的味道都不太纯正
It's never tasted right since the Blackout.
大断电
Blackout?
2022大停电
The Blackout of 2022.
你还真是什么都不记得
You really don't remember a thing.
那次断电彻底抹除了数据
It was a total data wipe.
改变了一切
Changed everything.
我说过我什么都不记得
I told you I can't remember anything.
但或许 我一开始就没有记忆
But maybe I never had any memories to begin with.
你为何会这么想
Why would you think that?
只有我们知道去哪找
We know where to find it. They don't.
那条小虫要是再现身
So if that little worm comes around again,
我们便杀了他
we slit his throat.
-发条消息给...  -卓夫
- That'll send a message to the  - Drove.
我想和你谈谈
Wanna talk with you.
你是在逗我吗
You gotta be kidding.
小猪猪 你想要啥 你又没我把柄
What do you want, little piggy? You ain't got nothing on me.
哇啊
Whoa--ow!
听说你和一个年轻女子有过冲突
Heard you had a run-in with a young woman.
她态度差 有黑莲花纹身
Bad attitude, tattoo of a black lotus.
我为啥要帮你这种人
Why would I help a pretty little piggy like you?
阿 哎呀
Ah! Geez!
行行行
Okay, okay! Ow!
也许我该把你切成片
Maybe I should slice myself off a piece.
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
警察事务 你们赶紧走吧
Police business. Now, move along.
不关我事
To hell with this.
总算清静些了
Just you and me now.
跟我说说那个女孩吧
Tell me about the girl.
你是想让我切下你的胳膊吗
You want me to slice your arm off?
另一只吗
The other one?
她完虐了我老大
She cut the boss up.
她太疯狂了
She's nuts.
持着一把武士刀
Carried a damn samurai sword.
你最好说详细些
You better give me more than that.
行 行
All right. All right.
算你厉害
You win.
她有一种科技
She had this...tech.
我们试图将其夺走 我们本来只是闹着玩
We tried to take it from her. We was just messing around.
之后 她主动找上门来
Then she comes back to kill us.
她脑子有问题
She's on bad neuro-stims or something.
你该对当地执法部门放尊重些
Might wanna show more respect for local law enforcement.
下次 我就不会这么客气了
Next time, I won't be so nice.
不会有下次了 小猪猪
Next time, you're gonna get it in the neck, piggy.
洛杉矶警察局调查人员拒绝评论
LAPD investigators have refused to comment on reports
班尼斯特参议员观看黑拳比赛时
that Senator Bannister was attending an unlicensed boxing match
惨遭不明凶手杀害一事
when he was killed by an unknown assailant.
班尼斯特在外星殖民地有着良好的声誉
Accolades for the senator came in from as far away as the Off-world colonies.
由于他长期的杰出工作
In a long and distinguished career,
他被视作
Senator Bannister was seen
无党派的基本人权捍卫者
as a non-partisan defender of basic human rights
被誉为真正的爱国者
and was hailed as a true patriot.
他就一狗屁玩意儿
He was a piece of shit.
弄清我设备里有什么了吗
Did you find out what's on my device?
还没
Not yet.
什么是复制人
What's a replicant?
复制人
A replicant?
是机器吗
A machine?
不完全是
Not exactly.
那是啥
Then what?
你为何关心这个
Why do you even care about this?
班尼斯特说
Bannister said so.
我是复制人
That I'm one of...them.
难道你信那个人渣的话吗
And you believe what that scum told you?
但假如...
But what if...
20年前 一家公司制造了人造人
20 years ago, a corporation made artificial people.
将其命名为复制人
Called them replicants.
期望他们干脏活累活时
Hoping they'd do all our heavy lifting
无半句怨言
without ever complaining.
别动
Hold still.
看着我
Look at me.
我来告诉你你是不是复制人
I'll tell you if you're a replicant.
向左上方看
Look up and to the left.
别眨眼
Don't blink.
你不是复制人
You're not a replicant.
假如你是Nexus8型 你会有一个序列号
If you were a Nexus 8, you'd have a serial number.
你要是6型 早就死了
6, you'd be long dead.
那我是怎么做到的
Then how did I do these things?
我是怎么
I can fight.
轻而易举打伤人的
I hurt a lot of people.
你要是还不放心
If you're still worried,
只有一种方法可以判定
there's only one way to tell for sure.
坐吧
Have a seat.
这叫Voight-Kampff测试
We call it Voight-Kampff.
能判断你是人类还是复制人
Tells if you're human or replicant.
复制人意志坚定
Replicants are tough as nails,
但他们外表与常人无异
but they look just like everybody else.
要怎么测试
What's it going to do to me?
别着急
Don't worry.
我只用问你几个问题
I'm just gonna ask you some questions.
可我记忆全无
I don't have any memories.
感觉可以回答的东西比记忆多
Feelings can tell more than memories.
感觉潜藏在更深处
They're deeper.
假如你是复制人
If you're a replicant,
你的情感会前后矛盾
your emotions will be marked by contradictions.
想象一下你的母亲
Picture your mother.
在你儿时的屋子里
In the house you grew up in.
她失望地看着你
She looks at you, disappointed,
说她不爱你
and tells you that she doesn't love you.
她从未爱过你
She's never loved you,
她后悔有了你
and she regrets ever having you.
为人母者不会说这种话的
A mother would never say that.
你正要去朋友公寓
You're passing a busy street corner
站在熙熙攘攘的大街上
on the way to a friend's apartment,
你看见垃圾箱旁有个小纸箱
and you see a small cardboard box next to a dumpster.
里面有一只虎纹小猫
Inside is a tabby cat, a kitten,
不是复制的 它有一双绿眼 鼻上有一个白点
a real one with green eyes and a white spot on her nose,
嗷嗷待哺
meowing for food.
我会带回家喂它
I'd take it home and feed it.
我爱猫
I like cats.
你为什么爱猫
Why do you like cats?
嗯
Hmm...
猫咪可爱 毛茸茸的
they're cute and fluffy.
你还记得恋爱的事吗
Can you remember being in love?
恋爱的感觉如何
How did it make you feel?
这个问题简单
That's easy.
他看我的眼神
The way he'd look at me...
我的心都快融化了
I thought my heart was going to burst.
那是一种美妙的感觉
It felt like... something wonderful.
纹好看点
Make it pretty.
别动
Stay still.
太棒了
That is so cool.
真好看
It's beautiful.
就当是
It's a gift.
纪念你崭新开始的礼物吧
To mark your new beginning.
你说的是我们的崭新开始吗
Don't you mean our new beginning?
别忘记我 艾尔
Don't forget me, Elle.
那时你几岁
How old were you?
记忆回来了
It's coming back.
那是我们第一次见面
That was when we first met.
他知道很多事
He knew so many things.
他告诉我 莲花代表纯洁
He told me that the lotus represents purity.
于是他就帮我纹了一个
So he gave me this tattoo.
但听说只有白莲花才代表纯洁
But only the white lotus is said to be pure.
错
No.
不同人有不同看法
That depends on perception.
你不必担心了
Don't worry.
你不是复制人
You're not a replicant.
你只不过是失忆了
You're just a girl with amnesia.
你的情感没有任何矛盾
Your emotions don't exhibit any contradictions.
休息会儿吧
Get some rest.
我出去喝一杯
I'm going out for a drink.
顺便给你带点吃的
I'll grab you some food.
加州在遭受了严重的气候变化后经济没有崩溃
Senator Bannister is the reason California still has an economy
这都是班尼斯特参议员的功劳
despite devastating climate change.
他是人民的英雄
A hero to the people.
英雄
A hero?
他毫无英雄气概
Wasn't a heroic bone in his body.
现在他死了 要撤销复制人禁令
Now that he's gone, it's going to be harder
难上加难
to remove the ban on replicants.
我还有不少能帮忙的朋友
I still have plenty of friends who can help me.
酒肉朋友吗
Friends made with money?
你是来羞辱我的吗
Is that why you came up here? To insult me?
还是来彰显你的自尊的
Or is this another talk about your pride?
我承认
I admit,
没有你 人们会挨饿
humanity would have starved without you.
你研究出了合成蛋白质
It was your research that led to synthetic proteins.
但要是没了钱和权的加持
But ideas mean nothing
你的想法便无从实现
without the money and power to actualize it.
既然上天不肯恩赐人们粮食 那么我给
I gave the people manna when heaven would not oblige.
要是谁有窃取丰功伟绩的能力
If a man is capable of stealing the credit for a feat of such enormity, I say,
那就给他时间
give him time.
再多的财富也无济于事
No amount of wealth can save him.
但你得借助我的财富
And you need my wealth
才能撤销复制人禁令
to remove the ban on those replicants.
这是大势所趋
Everything intended will happen.
也是上天的旨意
A god makes it so.
你自己听听
Listen to yourself.
你知道你现在说话像谁吗
Do you know who you're starting to sound like?
《上帝之城》 圣奥古斯丁
獾医生
Doc Badger.
洛杉矶警局的戴维斯警官
Officer Davis, LAPD.
问你几个问题
Have a few questions.
尽管问 我啥都没干
Whatever it is, I didn't do it.
你在附近见过一个纹着黑莲花的年轻女子吗
Young lady with a black lotus tattoo's been seen around here.
你觉得我整天都会
You think I spend all day looking?
注意别人的纹身吗
Looking at people's tattoos?
她带着数据器
Well, she was carrying a data drive
持着一把刀
and swinging around a sword.
一把武士刀
Samurai seef.
就在这附近
Right around here.
大家都说你是这片区会留意这种事的人
Everyone knows you're the man to see about these kinds of things in this part of town.
我要打烊了
It's time for me to close the store.
你要是不逮捕我的话
If you're not arresting me,
就去找别人吧
go bother other people.
回头联系你 医生
I'll be in touch, Doc.
什么
What?
起来 跑啊 你们这些劣质玩偶
Get off your asses and run, you two-bit dolls!
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
你懂规矩的
You know the rules.
我是个记者
Hey, I'm a journalist.
我既然来了 肯定得记录一下
If you don't document it, did it really happen?
结束了吗
Finished already?
这个距离打他们
There's no challenge
太没挑战难度了
just picking 'em off from this far.
要是他们再危险些
If they really are dangerous,
我们可以近距离猎杀
we could be hunting 'em up close.
听起来不错
Sounds like fun.
这些复制人生来就
These replicants are hardwired
对人类言听计从
to be fully submissive to humans.
快开枪啊
Come on. Just pull the trigger!
复制人
Replicants...
生来就
hard-wired...
对人类
to be fully...
言听计从
submissive?
这些东西完全不中用
Oh, these things are helpless.
我们想干嘛都行
Whatever we want, we do.
太过简单
It's too easy.
为什么
Why?
《Home》 - Walk off the Earth
♪ 我已厌倦 再难忍受 ♪
♪ I'm so tired, oh, so tired ♪
♪ 脑海里的那些声音 ♪
♪ All these voices in my brain ♪
♪ 陪我度过无数日夜 ♪
♪ Living through my normal, oh, so formal ♪
♪ 却使我精神错乱 ♪
♪ I swear they're driving me insane ♪
♪ 实在难以分辨是谁在撒谎 ♪
♪ Can't tell who's a liar come hell or high water ♪
♪ 我没在听 ♪
♪ I'm not listening ♪
♪ 喔噢 ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ 我要逃离这儿 ♪
♪ I'm getting out of here ♪
♪ 哦 不 ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ 我不放手 直至你开口 ♪
♪ I won't let go till you say so ♪
♪ 我已厌倦迷失 ♪
♪ I'm tired of being lost ♪
♪ 告诉我该如何回家 ♪
♪ Show me the way to get back ♪
♪ 回家 ♪
♪ Home ♪
♪ 我要回家 ♪
♪ To get back home ♪